Guide to the Daniel S. Greenberg papers, [ca. 1961-2010]
Greenberg, Daniel S. papers,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Daniel S. Greenberg papers, [ca. 1961-2010]
6993
Greenberg, Daniel S.,
24 cubic feet.
Research materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files consist of research materials from his books and other reporting.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Science journalist and author. Daniel S. Greenberg graduated from Columbia University in 1953. In 1961, he became the first editor of the "News and Comment " section of the journal Science. He also worked as a science reporter for the Washington Post. In 1971 he founded the Science and Government Report, a fortnightly review of government grants, reports, and activities in science. He served as its editor until 1997, when it was acquired by John Wiley & Sons. He also authored several books on the politics of science in the United States, including The Politics of Pure Science (1967), Science, Money and Politics (2001), Science for Sale (2007), and Tech Transfer (2010).
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files consist of research materials from his books and other reporting, including media clips, Congressional reports, transcripts, and agency reports, filed alphabetically by topic (with various subtopics, changes over time, etc.) Files also contain some interview notes, partial transcripts of interviews, and correspondence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Greenberg, Daniel S., 1931-
Subjects:
Science and state -- United States.; Science -- Political aspects -- United States.; Science -- Economic aspects -- United States.; Federal aid to research -- United States.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I: Miscellaneous Pamphlets, Clippings, Correspondence and Documents
Series II: News and Journal Clippings
Subseries Ia
Subseries Ib
Series III: University Information for "Science for Sale"
Series IV: Science and Technology Statistics
Series V: Scientific Misconduct
Series VI: Office of Technology Assessment
Series VII: Science and Government Report
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I: Miscellaneous Pamphlets, Clippings, Correspondence and Documents
  - St. Louis, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - AAAS, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - AAMC, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AAU, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ADX2, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - AMA, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Academic friends, top 100, budget, 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Committee, FDCA, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Accountability, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ag Reference, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alarmiit, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alternative Medicine, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alberts, Bruce, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Animal Rights, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Appeals to Politics, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arms Control, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ARPA, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Astrology, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Atkinson, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Awards and Nobels, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Backlash: environmental, nuclear, food warnings, 1979-1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Basic protective, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bell Labs, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bernthal, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Biomed- doubts, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bios, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Bio-terrorism, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Biotech and GM backlash, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Bizarre, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Bloch, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Breast Cancer, Army money, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Bromley, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Brookhaven, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Budget: Dems vs. GOP, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - BST, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Brown, CEO, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Budget Forecast, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bush report, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cancer statistics, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Campaign money, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Censorship, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Census, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ceremonies (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Characteristics, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Citation Index, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Civilizing science in relation with public political support, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Clinton, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cold-fusion, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Cold War, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Collaborative R and D, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Commercializing government, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Competitiveness, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Computing, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Conant (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Congressional Fellows, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Congress and Science, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Cosmos club, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Coverups: radiation, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Cradas, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Crime Tech, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Critical Technologies, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Critics of Science, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Culture, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Criteria- support, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Culture and science, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cures, treatments, good news and claims, 1997-2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - DARPAS, DOD, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - DOE, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Darsee, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Data sharing and restrictions, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - David, Ed, 1972-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Decade of brain, 1989-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Defense conversion, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Defense Science Board, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Democracy, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Department of science, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dingell, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Discovery, pace of, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - DNA register, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - DNA moratorium, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - DOD, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - DOD university forum, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Doubling, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Downsizing, 1994-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dual use and spinoff, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Stanford and UCSF, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - UK, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Earmarks, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - E-biomed, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Economic growth, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Economic return, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Ehlers repost, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Einstein (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Electronic grant application and review, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Elective politics, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - End of science, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Endowment, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Enemies cut (Nixon), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Engineering, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Environment, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Entrepreneur and venture capital, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Environmental security, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - EPSCOR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Establishment (science), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Ethics, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Evolution, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Export controls, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Facilities, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Factions, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - FASEB, 1997-1999 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - FDA, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - FOIA, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Faraday, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Federation of American Scientists, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Feder, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Frankenstein- fear of science, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Funding alternatives (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fusion, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Future in bones- bigger role for science, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Garwin, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gene hunting, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Geographic distribution, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Genome- Watson, Venter, etc., 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Gibbons, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Globalization, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Global warming dispute, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Gore, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Gould, Stephen J., 1999 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - GPRA, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Grant data, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - growth- new facilities and programs, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Gulf Syndrome, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Healy, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Health Scares, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - High energy physics, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Hi-tech industry and politics, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - HHMI, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hostility to science, 1998-2000 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - ISI stats, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - IIASA, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - ISI hot papers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Immigration, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - India, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Industrial research and development, 1995-1999 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Industry- basic, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Intellectual Property, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Innovation, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Internationalism, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - International cooperation, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Internet hackers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Interviews, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - ISI stats, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Inventors, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Jason, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Jobs, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Junk science, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Japan, 1986-1998 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Keyworth, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Knapp, Ed, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Koshland, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Lobbies, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Loweth (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Lane, NSF, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Law science, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Lawyers, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Liebowitz, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - LIGO, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Limits of science and medicine, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Maddox, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Malaria, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mathematics, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Medical journal- independence, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Meeting notes- MIT, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Medical education, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - McCarthy, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Mikulski, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Military research and competitive effects, 1986-1998 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - MIT, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Missile defense, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Morale, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Mullis, Kary, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - NAS, 1980-1998 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NATO, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NSF programs, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NSF founding statutory authority, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - NIMH, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - National Labs, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - National science board, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Nixon tape transcription, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - NRL archives, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nobels, 1982-2003 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Nuke test, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - OECD, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Oppenheimer, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - ORI, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - OSTP and presidents, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Paranormal, 1979-1990 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Patents, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Physics, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - PCAST, 1993-1999 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - PNGV, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Peer review, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - PhD Stats, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Pharmaceutical industry, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Philanthropy, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Pluralism of scientific agencies, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Policy studies, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Political and social involvement, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Political pressure in science, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Polygraph, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Pork, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Populist science movement, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Porter, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Post articles, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Post docs, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Predictions, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - PNGV, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Press, Frank, 1991-1998 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Prestige of science, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Priorities, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Privacy, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Prizes and Awards, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Professions, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Proposal pressure, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Public vs. private interest, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Publishing tats, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - RABI, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Regulation of science, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Religion and science, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Reports- use for advocacy, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Republican revolution, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Research America, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Research, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Resistance to change, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Restrictions on research, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Ridicule - science projects, 1998-2006 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Rifkin genetics, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Risk and health, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rogue research (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Russian science, 1997-1999 (Box 5, Folder 26-27)
  - SBIR, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - SSC, 1990-1998 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Sakharov, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Salaries and stipends, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Seti, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - SDI, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Science court, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Science press, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Science wars, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Shortfall, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Singer, Maxine, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Slutsky, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Social science, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Sovereignty science and self government, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Soviets, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Space shuttle, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Spallation, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Space station and space, 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Stability, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - State government research, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - State of union, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - State Department and Science, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Stem cells, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Stockpile steward, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Studies of science, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Superconductivity, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tax credit, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Teach vs. research, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Technology vs. science, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Technology transfer, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Tenure, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Trivelpiece, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Tuition, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Turf protection, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Two cultures, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Two thousand budget, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - UFO, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Universities, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - University money, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 18-19)
  - USUNS, 1977-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - VA, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Vapid Prose, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Varmus, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Venture capital, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Watson, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Whistle blow, 1988-1999 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - White, Bob, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Wolye, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Women's issues, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Wyngarden, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Bush and science, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - MD supply, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Entrepreneurship, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Obama- right place of science, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Space shuttle articles and booklets, 1977-1986 (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
  - Science debate410, 2001-2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Prepublication report copies, 2004-2009 (Box 7, Folder 9-11)
  - Corruption, 2004-2009 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - CHE blog, 2006-2008 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Conflict of interest (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Continuing medical education, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bush/Kerry and science, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 1-5)
  - Stem cells and money, 2005 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Research reports, 1983-2003 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - OTA revival, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - AUTM and reports, 2002-2005 (Box 8, Folder 10-13)
  - True church, alternative medicine, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 14-17)
  - Science in American life, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Public understanding of science, 1990s (Box 9, Folder 2-3)
  - State final reports, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Politics, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Johnson and Humphrey and science, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
  - Rufus Clement bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rubel, John H. bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Kistiakowsly, George bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Larsen, Finn J. bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Knudsen, Vern, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Lee, Russell Z. bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Press, Frank, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Nabrit, Samuel bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Johnson and Humphrey miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 17-19)
  - Medical project, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Citizens, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Radio spots, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Abel, Charles bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Gavin, James bio, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Science and technology miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 25-26)
  - NIH Correspondence and reports, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - NIH, OPASI, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - NIH Pamphlets and reports, 1993-2009 (Box 9, Folder 29-30)
  - Obama stimulus money, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - University patents, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - University building and money, 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Obama, science and stem cells, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Research fraud, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Corruption, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Conflict of interest, 2009-2010 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Research and development, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Technology transfer, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Series II: Newspaper and Journal Clippings
  - Subseries Ia
    - Abelson, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Abortion, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Academic fights, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Academic industry, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - ACS, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Accountability, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Agricultural research, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Aging, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Alberts, Bruce, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Animal testing, 1977-1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Alcoholism, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Atkinson, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Battleships, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Alarmism, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Alternative medicine, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Arts and Humanities chief, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Attaches- science and medicine, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Back pain, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Basic research, 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Battleships, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Bell Labs, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Breakthroughs, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Bilateral research and development, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Bromley, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Brown, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - BST, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Cannibalism, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Cheating, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Civil defense, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Carter, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Clinical trials, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Cloning, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Coffee, 1986-1999 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Cold fusion, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Commission on integrity, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Consensus meeting, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Coronary bypass surgery, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Cosmetics, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Cosmos club, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Cranberg- science ethics, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Creationism, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Cryptography, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - CTI, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Dentistry, 1981-1999 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Dingell, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Dioxin, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Disease of the month, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - DNA, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - DoD Universities, 1976-1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Defense of science, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Define prob. away, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Department of science, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Don't works, 1987-1999 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Drug abuse, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Drugs, pharmacist, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Einstein, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Economic indicators, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Education commission, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Elections, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Electronics, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Embargo technology, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Endowments, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Energy supply, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Employment, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Environment, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Environmental warfare, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Ethics, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Experimental technology, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Exports- hazardous, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - FAS/ACA, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Fat, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Federal employment, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Forms, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Foundation for International Scientific and Technological Cooperation, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Foxbat, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Foreign students, 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Fraud doctors, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - France, 1981-1990 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - FOIA, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Fusion, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Goldin- NASA, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Gramm, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Health policy, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Healy, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Healy, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Heimlich maneuver, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - High tech failure, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Hughes institute, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Human frontier, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Hundreds, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Iatrogenic medicine, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - Ingelfinger rule, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Inspector General, NIF, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - IIASA, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Infant formula, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - ISI, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Interferon, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Kessler, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Kevorkian, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Koshland, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lab tests, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Laetrile, 1977-1978 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Lane, NSF, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Lawyers, 1976-1996 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Left hand, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Love studies, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Mancuso, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Massey, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Mathematics, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Med school, 1978-2000 (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
    - Medicare, 1999 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - McCutchen, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Medal of Science, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Medical profession, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Mega Project, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Military medicine, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Mental health commission (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Microwave, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Middle East Water, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Military forces, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Military research and development, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Moscow embassy radiation, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Reverend Moon, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - National Association of Science Writers membership lists, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - NAS, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - New magazines, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - NIOSH, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - National Labs, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - National Science Board, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - NSF Organization, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - NIH budgets, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Neutron weapons, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Nuclear regulatory commission, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 41)